Anamika Rathore

DELHI (NCR)

Contact: 7291062668

Email: Anamika199318@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 18th Jan 1994

Dear Sir/ Ma'am,

This is in reference to the relevant job vacancy in your organization. I am writing to express my interest in joining your team.

My resume is enclosed for your review and consideration. To describe myself in nutshell, I am hardworking; ready to take up any challenge of life abreast with the latest trends and a team player with excellent communication skills.

Review of my credentials will indicate that I hold a Master Degree in Marketing(MBA) from Galgotias University, Greater Noida; and enriched with the knowledge of various aspects of the field like Google My Business, Adwords, Adwords Express, Competition Analysis, Pricing, Promotion Strategies, Selection of Marketing Channels, Product Life Cycle (PLC), ATL & BTL strategies, YouTube Premium. I also hold corporate experience of 5 years working with HDFC LIFE. Meritnation.com, Intelenet Global services pvt. Ltd.(GOOGLE PROCESS), Cognizant Technologies (YouTube Premium).

I am seeking a challenging job that would synergies my skills and knowledge with the objectives of the organization. Good academic record and outstanding communication skills are my key assets. Being a dedicated and focused individual, I am determined to add value to the organization I work for, through my compatibility skills and learning ability.

Professionally I am looking for an opportunity that will help me utilizing my skills in the above areas.

My detailed resume is enclosed herewith for your kind perusal and consideration.

I am confident that you would find my strong initiatives and commitments to excellence coupled with demonstrated experience and exposure ideal for the position.

I would welcome a personal meeting to further discuss your requirements and my ability to meet the same.

Thanking you for your consideration and forthcoming response.

Yours Sincerely AnamikaRathore

ANAMIKA RATHORE

Email id: anamika199318@gmail.com

MBA, (Marketing & Media management, 2014)

Language Proficiency: English & Hindi

Mobile: +91-7291062668

Place: Gurugram Experience: 5 Years



CAREER OBJECTIVE

To be a part of a reputed organization where I get an opportunity to use and enhance my talent and knowledge for development of both the organization and myself. I will continuously strive for higher achievements of my organization with the team efforts, my positive attitude and performance.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE (5 years)

Cognizant Technology Solutions (YouTube) Oct 2018 – till now

As a YouTube Premium Specialist my responsibilities are:

- Responsible to give support to YouTube Premium international clients.
- Troubleshoot the issues related with YouTube Premium, Google Play Music and YouTube Music Premium.
- Interact with clients through emails and provide them the best possible solution.
- Create connection with the customers according to their issues.
- Responsible to send the daily work reports of the team.
- Maintain quality scores, match monthly and quarterly targets of the cases handled.

INTELENET GLOBAL SERVICES PVT. LTD. (Google Client)July 2016- June 2018

From April 2017 to till now (Google My Business)

- Responsible to create feature-rich online listing on Google Maps.
- Optimizing Google my business accounts, by hours of operations, phone number, photos, Google maps, review links at no cost.
- Provide free website for Google my Business accounts.
- Improve SME business's local ranking by using Google My business.
- Lead generation for Google Adwords Express accounts.

From july 2016 to march 2017 (Google Adwords Express)

- As an online strategist for Google Adwords Express we have to generate business for Google Accounts.
- Responsible for generating revenue from online advertisements.
- Responsible for creating an account for SME's according to their requirements.
- Manage customer's account like target location, budget, and add creation.
- Responsible for budget management of customer's accounts including pay per click model

MERITNATION.COM EDUCATION COUNSELLOR Aug 2015-May 2016

- Educating customers about the online education product.
- Giving demos and presentations regarding the product.
- Generating the leads through calling & accordingly fixing up the appointments.
- Meeting Business targets through effective convincing and selling skill.

HDFC LIFE SDM (Corporate Agency) july 2014 – june 2015

- Responsible for sales of insurance policies.
- Responsible for generating business from assigned territory.
- Responsible to generate business from provided accounts.
- Documentation & briefing of the product.
- Generating policies and login it through POINT OF SALE.
- Maintain relationships with clients

Brand Kraft Marketing Group Summer Internship June2013 – July2013

Project title: Competition Analysis for generating business

- Responsibility to fix up new meetings with the client.
- Responsible to create a pool of more and more fresh talent with the company, by giving proper explanation about the plans and policies of the company.
- Implementing of various Marketing Strategies and Business development.

PROJECTS UNDERTAKEN

- Comparative study of CUSTOMER SATISFACTION TOWARDS WHATSAPP
- ATL & BTL advertising.
- A Study on marketing mix & competitive analysis of "Pure it" (HUL)

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

DEGREE	YEAR	COLLEGE/ UNIVERSITY	UNIVERSITY/BOARD	% / CGPA
MBA	2012-2014	Galgotias University Greater Noida	-	8.6 (C.G.P.A.)
BBA	2009-2012	Integral University Lucknow	-	73.00%
XII	2008-2009	Navyug Radiance Sr. Sc. School Lucknow	C.B.S.E. BOARD	65.5%
Х	2006-2007	RC Inter College Mainpuri	U.P. BOARD	64.00%

PROFESSIONAL ACHEIVEMENTS

- > Participated in various seminars organized by Galgotias University Greater Noida.
- > Participated in Blood Donation Camp on 28stJuly 2013, at Galgotias Campus
- Participated in debate competition, at Galgotias Campus.
- Actively participated in various events at school and college level.

CERTIFICATES

- Certificate of multimedia and web technology.
- > O Level from NIELIT formerly known as DOEACC SOCIETY.
- Certificate of IBM training.
- ➤ GOOGLE ADWORDS certified (Fundamentals)

STRENGTHS

Holistic Perspective: See bigger picture and keeping it simple.

Structured Thinking: Systematic Approach for problem solving.

Team Player: Strong team-building and team-leading abilities

Positive attitude: Strong determination and capacity to make things possible.

PERSONAL PROFILE

- Comprehensive problem solving abilities and dealing with people diplomatically
- Excellent verbal and written communication skills
- Willingness to learn.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Fathers Name : AmodRathore

Date-of-Birth : 18 Jan.1994

Nationality : Indian

Languages Known : English and Hindi

Date: Place: